We follow the money. You make it possible.
------------------------------------------

*  $35
*  $50
*  $100
*  Other

Donate Today

×

OpenSecrets Launches New State and Federal Lobbying Tool [Read the press release  ›](#)[](https://www.opensecrets.org/news/2024/01/press-release-opensecrets-launches-first-of-its-kind-tool-to-track-spending-on-state-and-federal-lobbying/)

We track the money. You make it happen.
---------------------------------------

OpenSecrets offers independent and nonpartisan reporting, a host of informative online tools to help you understand the role of money in politics and insightful profiles breaking down the important issues that matter. All of this is available for free and you can help keep it that way.

**Join our Summer New Donor Drive and help us hit our goal of 100 new donors by June 28!** Giving $1 or more will help ensure we can continue offering our services for years to come.

[Open Secrets following the money in politics](https://www.opensecrets.org/) Menu

* Candidates & Officeholders

* Elections & Fundraising Data

* Industries & Interest Groups

* Lobbying

Search

Go

Close

1. [Home](https://www.opensecrets.org/)
2. [About](https://www.opensecrets.org/about)

Privacy Policy
==============

About

1. [Mission](https://www.opensecrets.org/about) 
2. [About The Site](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/tour) 
3. [Board](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/board) 
4. [Our Team](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/staff) 
5. [Awards & Accolades](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/awards) 
6. [Funders](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/funders) 
7. [Editorial Independence Policy](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/editorial_independence_policy) 
8. [Statement on diversity, equity and Inclusion](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/dei_statement) 
9. [Financial Information](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/financial) 
10. [Annual Reports](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/report) 
11. [Employment](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/jobs) 
12. [Internships](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/intern) 
13. [Training Opportunities](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/training) 
14. [Testimonials](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/testimonial) 
15. [Privacy Policy](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/policy) 
16. [Contact us](https://www.opensecrets.org/about/contact) 

**Find Your Representatives:**

OpenSecrets.org Privacy Policy
==============================

OpenSecrets takes your privacy very seriously. OpenSecrets is the sole owner of the information collected from users on OpenSecrets.org. **OpenSecrets will not share, rent or sell personally identifiable information to any third parties**. You will never be sent marketing materials by OpenSecrets unless you explicitly opt-in.

Information you submit to our web site will be used to contact you if you have subscribed to our newsletter, if you have made a donation or if you respond to an action request made by OpenSecrets. Should you "unsubscribe" from a newsletter you will be permanently removed from our contact list.

OpenSecrets.org uses temporary session "cookies" (data that is generated on our web server and stored on your computer) for authentication and other purposes. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information and are deleted when the browser window is closed. A user may set his or her browser to disallow cookies. In such a case, some features of the website may not work as intended. In addition, third party social networking services and advertisements are displayed on OpenSecrets.org which may use cookies as well.

OpenSecrets.org uses Google Analytics, Quantcast, and Hotjar to learn how people use the site and to improve our services as well as Twitter and Facebook widgets for social sharing. We also collect standard log files from our systems to ensure the integrity of our services and for troubleshooting purposes. Included in these log files are the date, the IP address and the URL of the request. Log files are typically deleted from our servers after 90 days. Aggregate information that does not personally identify you may be shared with funders or potential future advertisers.

When this privacy policy is revised or updated, OpenSecrets will post the updated version, including the effective date of the revision or update, on OpenSecrets.org. It shall be construed that you accept and agree with the revised or updated privacy policy when you access and use the website for the first time after the publication of such changes. If you have questions about this policy, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.opensecrets.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

This privacy policy was last updated on July 10, 2014.

We follow the money. You make it possible.
------------------------------------------

*  $35
*  $50
*  $100
*  Other

Donate Today

Count Cash & Make Change
------------------------

Sign up for our newsletter to track money’s influence on U.S. elections and public policy.

Please enter a valid email address 

Do not fill this out if you are a person 

Sign Up

A 501(c)(3) tax-exempt, charitable organization

1100 13th Street, NW, Suite 800 Washington, DC 20005

(202) 857-0044

[\[email protected\]](https://www.opensecrets.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Except for the Revolving Door section, content on this site is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-Share Alike 3.0 United States License by OpenSecrets.org. To request permission for commercial use, [\[email protected\]](https://www.opensecrets.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
